// History Questions
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Cartographer is a person who makes:",
    answer: "11th",
    options: [
      "Maps",
      "Cartoons",
      "Caricatures",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "In which century Babur used Hindustan to describe geography of subcontinent?",
    answer: "16th century",
    options: [
      "18th century",
      "17th century",
      "16th century",
      "None of these"

    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Why do historians today have to be careful about the terms in the past?",
    answer: "Because the terms meant different in the past",
    options: [
      "Because they do not know the meaning of terms",
      "Because the terms meant different in the past",
      "Because the terms may have more than one meaning",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following is not the meaning of foreignerâ€™ in the past?",
    answer: "Indigenous",
    options: [
      "Ajnabi",
      "Indigenous",
      "Pardesi",
      "Stranger"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which type of people collected Manuscripts?",
    answer: "Wealthy people",
    options: [
      "Poor people",
      "Local people",
      "Wealthy people",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },
  {
  numb: 6,
  question: "Where were the manuscripts placed?",
  answer: "Both (b) and (c)",
  options: [
    "At home",
    "In libraries",
    "In archives",
    "Both (b) and (c)"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 7,
  question: "Which is the holy book of Muslims?",
  answer: "Quran",
  options: [
    "Gita",
    "Quran",
    "Adi-Puran",
    "Ramayana"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 8,
  question: "Prosperity in the subcontinent attract trading companies of which region?",
  answer: "European",
  options: [
    "Australian",
    "European",
    "Russian",
    "None of these"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 9,
  question: "Which language was spoken during 14th century in present Bengal region?",
  answer: "Gauri",
  options: [
    "Awadhi",
    "Gauri",
    "Telangani",
    "Lahori"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 10,
  question: "In which period did the number and variety of textual records increase dramatically?",
  answer: "700 to 1750",
  options: [
    "600 to 700",
    "700 to 1750",
    "700 to 800",
    "800 to 1000"
  ]
},

];
